<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[International Lyon Model United Nations]]></title><description><![CDATA[The International Lyon Model United Nations (ILYMUN) organization's website.]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 19:12:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[ILYMUN 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[2021 will be the ninth consecutive year in which the International School of Lyon and the Cité Scolaire Internationale de Lyon collaborate…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/about/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;2021 will be the ninth consecutive year in which the International School of Lyon and the Cité Scolaire Internationale de Lyon collaborate to organise ILYMUN. The conference usually takes place around the 30th, 31st January and 1st of February, in the prestigious ‘Hôtel de Région Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes’ (1 Esplanade François Mitterrand, 69269 Lyon, Cedex 02); however, due to the Covid-19 pandemic it will be held virtually this year on the 28th and 29th of January. We have invited keen and bright high school pupils to join us to debate and take action!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 20th century technological revolution, and especially the invention of the internet, brought about a new wave of globalization and the creation of a new space called the “cyber world”. The Covid-19 pandemic has shown how much we rely on technology and to what extent we are all connected. As the cyber world affects so many aspects of our lives, it must be considered when working towards the United Nations’ goals. The cyber world is a new frontier for which we need to develop institutions that are lawful, inclusive and fair. Our conference will focus on the United Nations’ Sustainable Goal 16, “Peace, Justice, and Strong Institutions” with debates focused on strengthening our cyber institutions. This brings us to the following questioning, this year’s theme: “Cyber world: Are truth, justice, and peace in the balance?”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that by involving youth in finding solutions and taking action, we can make a difference. Therefore, in addition to our core MUN committees, we will once again host the Action Assembly, in which students represent themselves rather than countries in order to work towards real change in their local communities, striving for change through direct action. Additionally, ILYMUN will also be hosting the ‘Youth Conference’ for middle school students from the Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will also offer the Model International Court of Justice (ICJ), a forum that mediates conflicts between two nations by reflecting on treaties, international conventions, and international law. The ICJ is a unique and enriching experience for delegates who wish to try something different to ordinary committees, particularly for those interested in pursuing a career in law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, we vow to make ILYMUN 2021 an unforgettable and thrilling experience for all its participants!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;History&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking inspiration from FERMUN in Geneva and THIMUN in the Hague, two students from the Cité Scolaire Internationale, Pierre Mohamed and Kaelan Tardy, reached out to students at the International School of Lyon in order to organise the first ILYMUN conference in 2013. Most of the schools participating in that first conference are now regular participants in our annual conferences and many have gone on to form their own MUN clubs and conferences inspired by ILYMUN. We’re delighted to see these developments: signalling that communities are truly working together towards the bettering of our world!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Our Values&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;1. Inciting Action&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our core objective is to bring about change. Outside of the MUN debates, we hope to extend the resolutions our students conceive, and apply them to the real world. Indeed, by taking action, we hope to contribute to bettering our international community by giving life to delegates’ ideas, with hope of striving towards a greater future. In the light of such, we encourage our delegates to educate themselves regarding these issues, both local and global, and to directly act upon them, externalising ILYMUN’s outreach upon our impaired societies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;2. Enriching Education&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe that MUN conferences should aim to educate the participants, providing them with essential skills such as public speaking, collaboration with others and critical thinking. MUN opens one’s mind and encourages in-depth reflections on our complex world. ILYMUN helps students grow and become global citizens. Here is a quote from one of our friends at INOMUN in Lille that captures our view of MUN: “The aim of debating is to resolve problems with words, without violence, without deaths. We, high school students, are the next generation. We have to act, we have to do something. An MUN conference won’t literally change things, but it is a way to sharpen our critical minds and our intelligence in order to take over our parents’ generation. In order to bring peace.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;3. Constant Innovation&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ILYMUN has matured since its inception by the virtue of original projects, developed every year. Of course, the central issue of the conference varies from year to year, with new branches and new committees created to bring diversification and an improved experience. Undeniably, the feedback from you, fellow participants, permits us to improve an important number of aspects of the conference, making it finer each year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;4. Human Experience&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most diplomats tell you that the most efficient decisions, those which actually change the world, are taken in convivial moments after a day of debate. This is wholly legitimate. Therefore, we keep in mind that an MUN conference is an opportune moment to meet new friends. A few essential factors, unique to ILYMUN, allow you to have real exchanges: small committees (from 20 to 100 persons), country delegations made up of different schools, housing with host families and, of course, social events!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;5. By Students, For Students&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though a very small team of adults supervises our agenda and the organisation of ILYMUN, every aspect of our conference — the vision, planning and execution — is done by high school students who are doing their best to provide middle school and high school delegates and their MUN directors the best possible MUN experience and a professional conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;6. Social and Ecological Engagements&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bearing in mind the ILYMUN 2016 conference resolutions to tackle Climate Change, we take concrete action to save the Planet, by respecting environmental values. We use a minimal amount of paper and transfer to digital as frequently as possible. We strive to be role models for a green conference.&lt;br/&gt;
The past several years we also have committed to debating the work and the value of various NGOs in our General Assemblies. Delegates then make a vote that leads to real action. The NGO that wins the majority vote receives a financial donation from ILYMUN. This donation is made possible by the wonderful support of our sponsors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;7. Sponsorship&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To make ILYMUN truly outstanding, we rely on generous sponsorship from institutions as well as private companies and individuals. We are currently sponsored by the Région Auvergne Rhône-Alpes who have generously provided their premises for the event. By financially helping ILYMUN, you will be effectively helping us reach our goals of providing a professional conference and encouraging young people to work towards positive changes in our world. For more information, click here to view our sponsor’s brochure (in PDF format). If you or your company are interested, our Public Relations Team is here to answer all of the questions you might have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact: tom.badou@csianglo.org&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Action Assembly]]></title><description><![CDATA[A unique committee where your voice is heard! What is Action Assembly ? The Action Assembly (AA) is very different from other committees at…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/action-assembly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/action-assembly/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A unique committee where your voice is heard!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What is Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Action Assembly (AA) is very different from other committees at ILYMUN. In this unique committee, you will not be debating real-time UN motions in the name of nations. Instead, the debates are more down-to-earth and relatable. They invite individual reflection. In the AA we debate motions that directly impact our way of life and delegates represent themselves (or corporations, political figures, etc. of their choice, depending on the theme).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the name implies, the Action Assembly’s purpose is to &lt;em&gt;take action&lt;/em&gt;. For this reason, each year, the committee works together to develop a statement of action or action plan, that will empower conference participants to take action on an attainable scale. It’s all about our generation being true actors of change.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What is this year’s theme ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; This year’s conference theme is **Cyber World: Are truth, justice and peace in the balance? **The Action Assembly will focus on the following three topics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Internet Relationships&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Cyber Activism&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;- The Impact Of The Internet On The Press&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a “digital” generation and it’s time we take more control of this aspect of our everyday lives. It’s up to us to develop frameworks and guidelines for the cyber world we live in.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What are we going to do ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; This year, the committee will produce a video in which volunteer delegates explain what they have learnt about the three topics, and what can be done to make positive changes. Given our &lt;em&gt;Cyber World&lt;/em&gt; theme, we hope to post the video on the ILYMUN YouTube Channel, and Facebook and Instagram accounts. The committee will also create a poster for delegates to put up in their respective schools, and to reach out to a wider audience about the topics discussed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The video and poster will help each and everyone of us to raise awareness, to take action on a scale that is attainable for students, and to share the knowledge that we have acquired at ILYMUN 2021.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;How do we prepare for the Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chairs have prepared a Research Report which gives delegates:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;- more details on the organization of the committee&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;- general information on the topics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;- sources for additional research&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;- questions to reflect on&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, we expect our delegates to have thought about their personal opinions on the topics, as well as have done research on one or more companies, political figures, or countries they will be representing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Why should YOU join the Action Assembly ?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; This is the committee in which your own voice is heard. The AA works &lt;em&gt;as a team.&lt;/em&gt; We are all on an equal footing, learning together. The AA &lt;em&gt;takes action&lt;/em&gt; towards &lt;em&gt;real change&lt;/em&gt;. The AA explores different points of view and hosts relevant conversations which lead to fulfilling debates. The issues are interesting and challenging. We can relate personally to these cyber issues. Unlike the other ILYMUN committees, our fight for change goes beyond the three-day conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;So…join us in the Action Assembly and promote action in the world!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Articles]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a href=”https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/guest-speaker-interview-tarek-eleiwy-27274647353c“>Click here…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/articles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/articles/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;title&gt;ILYMUN&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Mini ILYMUN Interviews&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the occasion of the Mini-ILYMUN conference, we had the great opportunity to interview Gaëlle Gormley, founder of the association Act for Ref and Tarek El, a refugee from Syria who came to France in 2014. Discover what they had to share about the conference&apos;s theme: refugees:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;[https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/guest-speaker-interview-ga%C3%ABlle-gormley-df8ffbbcc418](https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/guest-speaker-interview-ga%C3%ABlle-gormley-df8ffbbcc418 &quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/guest-speaker-interview-ga%C3%ABlle-gormley-df8ffbbcc418&quot;)&quot;&gt;Click here to read Gaëlle Gormley&apos;s interview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x3C;a href=”&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/guest-speaker-interview-tarek-eleiwy-27274647353c&quot; title=&quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/guest-speaker-interview-tarek-eleiwy-27274647353c&quot;&gt;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/guest-speaker-interview-tarek-eleiwy-27274647353c&lt;/a&gt;“&gt;Click here to read Tarek El’s interview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Mini ILYMUN: Refugees&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout the mini-conference of ILYMUN, our delegates were able to discuss important issues regarding the key relations between refugees and technology, covid or women rights. Discover more about these paramount topics our respective articles on medium:
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&amp;#x3C;a href=”&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/refugees-and-the-impact-of-covid-19-7074c3bdbd67&quot; title=&quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/refugees-and-the-impact-of-covid-19-7074c3bdbd67&quot;&gt;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/refugees-and-the-impact-of-covid-19-7074c3bdbd67&lt;/a&gt;“&gt;Click here to read about refugees and the impact of covid-19&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x3C;a href=”&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/empowering-refugees-through-technology-f4c93d208f96&quot; title=&quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/empowering-refugees-through-technology-f4c93d208f96&quot;&gt;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/empowering-refugees-through-technology-f4c93d208f96&lt;/a&gt;“&gt;Click here to read about empowering refugees through technology &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x3C;a href=”&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/protecting-the-rights-of-refugee-women-8b957a163676&quot; title=&quot;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/protecting-the-rights-of-refugee-women-8b957a163676&quot;&gt;https://medium.com/mini-ilymun-refugees-moving-towards-better-world/protecting-the-rights-of-refugee-women-8b957a163676&lt;/a&gt;“&gt;Click here to read about protecting rights of women refugees&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Journée de la Terre : Un appel à la préservation de la planète&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;À l&apos;occasion de la Journée de la Terre 2021, notre équipe de presse, ainsi que l&apos;équipe de presse de MUNNISA, ont créé un article sur la signification, l&apos;histoire et les célébrations de la Journée de la Terre.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@ilymun/earth-day-a-call-to-preserve-the-planet-b16d522cd3a2&quot;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;ILYMUN 2020 THEME: Water, a Thirst for Change&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Articles series: An Introduction to Water Issues &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ilymun-2020-theme-water-a-thirst-for-change&quot;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Guest Speaker 2020 : Jean Louis Etienne&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;The South Pole is where all the meridiens of all the countries come together. It is the land of international peace.&quot; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ilymuns-guest-speakers/dr-jean-louis-etienne-777c7922e72&quot;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Our written press team investigates the Humans of ILYMUN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the first day of ILYMUN, many people arrived, most of them strangers to us. At first, only one thing seemed to be in common: their smile. So we became inquisitive: why were they here, and what was making them smile so much? Here’s what we found out. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ilymun-inside-the-conference/ilymun-attendees-experience-70059aceca39&quot;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;ILYMUN : Inside the conference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Committee reports, articles, and more! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/ilymun-inside-the-conference&quot;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Training Day November 31st 2019&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Organization of ILYMUN is a very large undertaking and requires a lot of people to cooperate and work together in order to assure the quality of the whole conference. On november 30th, training day was a way to prepare all teams; press, admins, logistics just to name a few, to ensure that we could have the best possible conference for everyone involved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/training-day-committees/training-day-november-31st-2019-4f5b98525e2&quot;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Behind the Scenes of ILYMUN: MUN club at the CSI&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Model UN Club has been held at the Cité Scolaire Internationale of Lyon for many years. Students get together every Thursday, after school, to debate various topics, often inspired by ongoing events. Ranging from a motion on measures to protect forests, in light of the Australian bushfires, to resolutions on the refugee crisis, students are brought to confront ideas in a setting imitating a United Nations assembly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/getting-to-know-ilymun/behind-the-scenes-of-ilymun-mun-club-at-the-csi-f4d202c8248a&quot;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;ILYMUN PREPARATIONS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From January 30th to February 1rst, students from all over the world will gather to debate water issues, United Nations-style, at ILYMUN; an annual conference organized for students, by students. ILYMUN will be hosting the debate around water with the following committees: Security Council, Historical Security Council, Science and Technology, World Health Organization, Environmental, UNDP, Human Rights, Territorial, Action Assembly, International Court of Justice, Special Conference: focus on islands, Youth Conferences, and naturally, the General Assembly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/getting-to-know-ilymun/ilymun-preparations-5295de8c26cc&quot;&gt;See more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; If you want to see all of our articles: &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@ilymun&quot;&gt;Click here for link to medium.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Committees & Issues Debated]]></title><description><![CDATA[ILYMUN 2021 Security Council Protecting the Democratic Process Technology: Both Propagating and Fighting Extremism Historical Security…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/committees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/committees/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2021&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ynWRCqZR049EAfcMT2LlKtpX6ifBDY63/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Protecting the Democratic Process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1e1Yhd2GtuT0l6YxPYTv4LG665rcMdivs/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Technology: Both Propagating and Fighting Extremism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gulf War&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1eWfcabol7mlhTVj_5DQm0nybc827nCjp/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Revelations of Edward Snowden&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1CfEDEuCAZWo4h2oBpWNP3IFp-Nfrh06y/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The Rwandan Genocide: April to July 1994&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Council of the European Union&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ft_7oWOiNLtZFI7EdTC-71kQ-0sV0QzR/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;GAFAM: Protecting Europe’s digital sovereignty and integrity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UF9K0gOSFyxRxcTa1S-vpyJ1nqVMfTU1/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Connectivity: The challenge of creating a 5G wireless network, targeting areas with little or no network coverage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UNESCO- Focus on Press&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/15fkxt7KIoF4rgEgrbRSy2Fcrd6hZupzP/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Protection of Whistleblowers and Journalists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1zs86K-WgIY6eunnFObEYNbj_3RNgkvmX/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Free and Fair Press&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Human Rights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1bxhhQHdjxLkiAjcjhvjrZY3Y7KGs1Bry/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Censorship and Misinformation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1v8rMr11o_b6t8Gew2ooZcQ-7smBR9Noh/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Control of Personal Information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1v0IMA7mhemF6AeIvkosOinGDOZLJ_zkJ/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Invisible Pollution of Cyber Activity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1xr9ktgzJG28H-98dbXVuDB4OuqP0rc33/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Materials for Cyber Activity: Resources and Waste&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1XOeaLpt93_r-CarpIu7bwlYBXSs5NLZ9/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HEfnJbrBJLZL1eW0ksLUwQYuqSgyxtiz/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Cybersecurity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;World Health Organisation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ONwv1dF6T23s47v8Phxyz7XtexyuGT-O/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Health and the Cyber World&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1V6d22rPEKdif2xP3xbv1gkxlD4AauHPi/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Data: Strengthening Collection, Accuracy and Diffusion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1dpnBxgHm42_HkdPtRXnbVIoevF7T6uWt/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Ethics of Internet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1EYXiNTR0zHDDKoHBHZMg39o0KUA3dAJk/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Equity and Empowerment in/through the Internet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Economic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1P4rcFp04BRZ2mIflvHHo2CFqPNYIjzPp/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Transparency and Accountability in Cyber Finances&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ahLmwRS59fMRTinJXRo_DesI-Y0Nc2cS/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Work in the Cyber World: Inclusive, Sustainable and Decent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1sHPDG92C51z6KTMbtrkhmuUgSoVcbUFs/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internet relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activism on social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The relationship between between digital press and the public opinion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ICJ&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Russian interference in the 2016 U.S. elections:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;USA vs Russian Federation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Execution of the Iranian General by a U.S. drone strike:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Iran vs USA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Youth Committee&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1BLI1i__tw6BfEzJs1n-pKigHykoJLL2s/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1l7OUyZuQlnLA39Poyq3YCVeQ-1SymhGA/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Cyber Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/11BSHRIy-_SnFTUrFPtvQAY0oWBdVLAvp/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Invisible Pollution of Cyber&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1iS8Ol7Mj3u99coROVS-DPFCbTqX9FOz7/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Materiels for cyber activity Resources and Waste&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2020&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1xE6aZLvG1Ny4ubyC6dXIDn50AhaKljMu/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Marine Biodiversity &quot;&gt;Marine Biodiversity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ORcW91arQOU911crNGqKYg_pszmnOwiQ/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Tackling Organised Crime at Sea &quot;&gt;Tackling Organised Crime at Sea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1pmp1jjEHhdxtkd_YgNthYbg6bgMK69Hx/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;The South China Sea &quot;&gt;The South China Sea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/13ErhxmXVA_J8wGFDmHzDsIO0L3RJw8d5/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Water Scarcity &quot;&gt;Water Scarcity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1IbD555VApooD9WxILr5FTlJ5NPYlaxca/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Suez Canal Crisis: 1956 &quot;&gt;Suez Canal Crisis: 1956&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ijQtGtj6ZLRRpfVkqBZYqFZ3hk9WD4wC/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Turkish Invasion of Cyprus: 1974&quot;&gt;Turkish Invasion of Cyprus: 1974&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gRf_SYAgJMQhDqng8jJxPXVYcrIhj6j2/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Falkland Islands War: 1982&quot;&gt;Falkland Islands War: 1982  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Territorial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1JPTm-hU8FAg_zU9yui7ztL_CMxXBdzMw/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Arctic Waters &quot;&gt;Arctic Waters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1qJUbqiJSmdjkgfDk2mS9mfn8cgTBTX12/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Transboundary Waters &quot;&gt;Transboundary Waters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Environmental&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/13xnksv3_KyspxsbIVDY01pcPsWyTV1qL/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;The Great Pacific Garbage Patch&quot;&gt;The Great Pacific Garbage Patch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Ggr84M6fr7j2Abtau6_W1N4WalrE44nS/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Conservation and Management of Freshwater Sources&quot;&gt;Conservation and Management of Freshwater Sources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Science and Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gYkJgXdCxBgoPLjD0NXVwIIUUraTTgKA/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Improving Ocean Health&quot;&gt;Improving Ocean Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1lNJRCBKNqMxPY-Qc5jeuPm7rKQ5VkjGd/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Water as a Sustainable Resource&quot;&gt;Water as a Sustainable Resource&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Human Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/19YxsG1oQgpDrNRH3nTY9R9VsdJXlRQHX/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Embedding Gender Equity in Water Policies&quot;&gt;Embedding Gender Equity in Water Policies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1LQyznmaGxedTs7TcnelhI3t-QOLwtGFg/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Governance of Indigenous Peoples Water Supply&quot;&gt;Governance of Indigenous Peoples Water Supply&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;UNDP&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1mESK0bfmxm3da8OHkcr1l9E7JtHBT9ji/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Disaster Relief &quot;&gt;Disaster Relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/15Z_nb1e9r_obKzT3gTqafO9YTt-Eamkd/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Extraction, Trade and Allocation of Water Sources &quot;&gt;Extraction, Trade and Allocation of Water Sources &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1AxQWSLIX5yAAvfUQ7np9dqt03uYcpkvf/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Prevention and Management of Droughts &quot;&gt;Prevention and Management of Droughts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;World Health Organisation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1-jUpKHROBn0NusqwU6KlYNmtggoq2pp6/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Guaranteeing Water Safety &quot;&gt;Guaranteeing Water Safety&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1VSlzEh_apGEQJbhEygtTc4bVdkJSeGqF/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Water Scarcity &quot;&gt;Water Scarcity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Lvhhzu3ZiQOArdY8nnPliEURmOpnw-kE/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Water Over-Consumption; Water Pollution; Sanitation&quot;&gt;Water Over-Consumption; Water Pollution; Sanitation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Conference: Focus on Islands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1WLYtn_7Ycf1bQpIGfQDgaBZc4HAZakYQ/view?usp=sharing&quot; title=&quot;Special Conference: Focus on Islands &quot;&gt;Special Conference: Complete Research Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2019&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1qkUgtF8VtI-1rtgB1ZAuAVdSUOHjYUrFGgHNi0uC324/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The Respect of the Fundamental Rights endowed to all by the charter of the United Nations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1JXxAY4CA24UUkkP_GXeS0xmZeEOyUQis8b0RZzABVFI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The issue of the Rohingya people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Bk0rYlO2twnUMtdF4O-LP50TsrBkdgufrcv7KnGXTNI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Working towards a unified Bosnia Herzegovina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/18hupxkrwzHScvhqzwxk6pJdrg2ELnQgUEOkJOt5GL60/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The right of nations to have nuclear arms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/15jSnRJdVmLW6Q8G2gXQFsNLZLSbSuR24yyJyMUlvWyA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The recognition of the state of Israel and its membership in the UN; May 1948&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/103B3qeFI_Cpgl5duP-LEMJUmqqx-asGS-ME7fEEZVfw/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Drafting the Nuclear Non Proliferation Treaty; August 25, 1967&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1QWu3Mve1AM5KwXo44uzsrLrHTZXMFOL647kCM5ReBVg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Rwandan genocide; April 30, 1994&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Territorial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1vx2_SiD5jDIl4q8egVI6O8CQevIKeovu?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Sharing global resources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This committee will work towards the creation of multiple resolutions regarding specific resources (water, minerals, forests, oil, etc.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Environmental&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1U8cf6xz2wrHoDLiY8RCxvKtesgxBw9eI53Ca6z-z_78/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The pollution “market”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FqmpqxPqeKCTYneaEkjQO2JwNzcrBfn3UKF3yaVv1uI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Sustainable development: a balance between economic growth and the protection of natural resources and ecosystems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Economic&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1LemTIRZi04H3lZ_wmLfVXPOHycZmEOtQj_7mRtiz_N4/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Equality in the workplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1V_1XyON8PeQRiLjGuj6oF7g5cxVBwQnL6e0n2Cvu_NI/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing poverty as a step towards equity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Social&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1gB_iBYlp2Y94Hb7GCLz-xiD0EapQeOuoBcQJowRXry4/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing discrimination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NppMAPJd3eL2EJZyIi_hrcJGylNP4mGPMQYF4ygaaL0/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Universal healthcare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Human Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/15cjGASjC7M3KYvXZpdfN7TuideWbrrqNoFstYLZ1e8g/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Police brutality and discrimination of minorities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1aeWUQiIxcmpIqkjvQdKMje5wDA689QazK14q_IgEbpE/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;The protection and the rights of migrants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Conference: Focus on Children&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WxAz5GyxWxopmVKHk4CrSZDzGBMgnxGYxg-wehL_H9o/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Healthcare and mortality rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1F_TauSK7R69Atw3TLb9eVE7h92Uw2wafzVdDrK5ZDqU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Protecting the rights of the child&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1tZDIYwpEVeVViKR7CUm9tT2pMXNng1h0p3GK8jj1YvM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Education&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1vv7VzZJn6NxrkroLLDJklqCBCoMpU9lI/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Gender inequalities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1gKMtw16cSMB8GVLk4zcqFfpEr0VeDzwT/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Unequal access to culture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/14HGBEwQ27aglY0XsY0taXj-CVV_4mZc8/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Unequal access to health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Conference: Focus on Women&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/12yJnfdllyckCDxFvDEvetgzuKSxD6KZcpe5Tzgo5NuQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Reducing gender inequalities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1xmQUWaLW3abFrF_4Oe7sA0oCTSbe8elKDFYeTKuYBuc/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Empowering women&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2018&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;ilymun2018&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;card card-body&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1mZMZYBlwidT05QvGHQ9xlfu0ekoi9rk6zjsPJEv4Uyg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Securing cities against acts of terrorism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WfCUn79gEK1wfHmG1iDHeQaTSsYIH2L8S5ot35Eyvtw&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection of civilians in civilian war zones, Aleppo, Syria&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1G21BI9YQUw3X0Wzb3CU1ZHbwXZthTG8pHpem6GYvEf4&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of Chechnya, Russia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1Hvv0HmaHtO5PgfuZctBPu9WvQX3wCZ3GvYiumvQ70fQ&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Securing cities against acts of terrorism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WfCUn79gEK1wfHmG1iDHeQaTSsYIH2L8S5ot35Eyvtw&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Historical Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Korean War: June 25th 1950&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1ofAMq6jOINqo5MDwylQlruItBGY1i1JaagcZC7vIzy8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cambodia: 30th April 1977&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15gfOuBJU6axa2A5978mhCZvjUJ9gW9P7cDwLs58J9Ws&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approaches to preserving cultural heritage within urban areas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1yQVM_FBsfvqMmsU4ztByieBj1uoU2qSZ0S8jADA8-1k/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protecting UNESCO historical cities from ravages of war and siege&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1iOE6PqVWBeYm6bvlaMxOqTPltoLvGguDPOrr4Ur5vJ0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Development&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The issue of informal settlement in rapidly developing urban areas in LEDCs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15vGmQnWv0Vhcv8KOztD0ux42-YId_QUiADNYeYn-5M0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The implementation of the goals of Agenda21 in urban areas of LEDCs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ONzB7-WWQ1mkQf7vn63qCMDF_hxJ48XSqPRoSXeRXl4&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;ECOSOC&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meeting the demands of an ageing population in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1chez1NA9OfuKeifwQvAplvj1tMU8qBnE23NZvlBfdCc&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Problems faced by megacities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=14zZ5vGypUp7YCgsPJy4EJO2tYHmDOrbUM4zXtzHWsk8&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Environmental&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measures supporting cleaner and greener cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12ZaZ0-wPsHgWUwj5i-PGyW5r8z-eqR2sAuhRyFcDGfE&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Climate change and disaster risk in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1ftJKk7jDNfgueYvPC96v_tIQq4wZegQ4U9htpbzG8n0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Science and Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The use of renewable energy sources in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WcB2lZiM8ni9MdoGWdgwhny7rNA3NgJEiqYeu8t33L8&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of smart cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1WbKnKi6XCHrhC7rC0Xjy-d9VuHVqdr_Ca1US3FKAjy0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Special Human Rights Conference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protecting the rights of refugees in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1_CcCkOBmwn4yufRlR7562WnY-r_K5IQCp0UnBSMD4Dg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Providing equal access to basic services&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1IW8y1Juw0iq0f1TJWIBqsUtejFS4F1PL5COOCFjgVPg&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;International Court of Justice&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;War crimes in Aleppo, Syria&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1sl5eCsLmO3_NCGIemvTk-T2U-H5hXLd4&quot;&gt;Click here to access related documents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Action Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integration of marginalised people&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1NBnTTprGfyHc6d5KFvxza-CZ4r1NkitEOELSjdo5nnQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integration of young migrants in cities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12qfnMMEA1NnHMBmipwSDE90fj6SOMRc8GMBM_Q7fqQ0&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cities studied:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1okaRCumLKkeNyRZ3nWfLZcVGWRiiEl2zfN9Z0IXB1Oo&quot;&gt;Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1QgSdg_L12vo-wz9M2rEJskW8mcZHR6cCblHMt2oMBJw&quot;&gt;Mumbai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1YoxL2mqNX6s9I4AmWEjr5snIj0O4Lv2DX_dqnJeDElQ&quot;&gt;Nairobi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=15GFPaeEvgWaLs-1zRL_Eh8oz9aXs31xCUgVYa5eM6pY&quot;&gt;Paris&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1wmM2UqYtYNEqzEjyeOsGGrm_EjcyvUc89CkYlTB2s8Q&quot;&gt;Tehran&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/a/csianglo.org/document/d/1FrMZtA-JTyhmuWY7r1KR9aQkanWa624tayZhtzNhDXU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;section&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ILYMUN 2017&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;ilymun2017&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;card card-body&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;General Assembly&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1JpfiHrOpacGmjmENI21GCwWCWs_TIxGUhWpqf2FvjyE/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Security Council&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technological governance and democracy &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fFy1aYFiNdMknKTYWEMKZAm0wf1vN6b7U-9lSfw9pLo/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cyber warfare &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1L-ddWxrcGid-6M8u50kyifalEp0q1ZEMk7OQPSnGWGw/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Issue of security vs. privacy &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1SATkNofvVAD0ya_kvjteKJhl_UCql-Mr3Oj0z-xhzAA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting heritage sites from armed conflicts &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1PYhItq2k8Ivk7c3NCOxN7Yfsuj9QrB0hKBnIt_-Mvf8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural Memory&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mass media’s effect on culture &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/194KxwpDGT188KWo9nR35hHJlZPpZDKOrXBpi05NKE9E/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting heritage sites for and from tourism &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CutMrkE8Ir6P8Mi9PDb_NkTMMR7c0_yBFykZNKZuzb0/edit?pli=1&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Claims to historical artifacts and documents &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1gSQQLI_spdai3CQcy5QREEGCg4xKb1qPzKi4pnvGrOY/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Resource Management&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The issue of the “brain drain” &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1SoEDeW2_gExktLlmlgySDUVmzkuLXHVi-0oNq8x1MN8/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing food distribution &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Mzok1oXPNmea4IHnLun3Hk5dSGD99KvxTjHm137FWcg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing ocean resources &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fruxIZRd14gTQyColguNlt9aEH0xh8MXHc8_9hPoDTQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EcoSoc&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reducing technological disparities to promote economic equality &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FOu9K0sf-mR-DK_rQx7XmQ7co-W8YzBSTabXa0qlUSQ/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economic power of technology &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1cPK5M5lQ8nJxrpiy2PYax2vRjjngl1CE4dB81SRQslM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fighting poverty and inequality in a globalized society &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1wJTKM2eaxAqzEtsRXiDmbQcUSpSZUNYyyRPgvzROYLA/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cultural Identity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting and promoting indigenous cultures &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Oy7pXLwl4EBTnj1Sl1sflq4IC4UxifncOZXVOOYa3qk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining cultural identity in a globalized world &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FDbZI44kTnZ0yblKXa6UhrZs6GXeb1-9lM6ZxtzTNKk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protecting human diversity in the face of biotechnology &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1pmF2MVwCxDRyFrpJHsnv4Ab-vXxhgMzeOBdzRRKRghg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Migration&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fighting human trafficking and providing safe migration &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/11ebC2Xr67S4895I1hNRLwUOETtefDb9s9dnwroBFJ4w/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rights of refugees &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0a_hZsHRAFFbWhqa1JxdUNjUF9maTNTdWFZWWFKUEVZVzRF/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The role of borders and freedom of movement &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1V6BbkQoi9qlu8Lhjff8N9kVgfo36j5NZnBrcVt8Oh0M/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Human Rights&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting gender equality &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1g-_PCbeJv_IA15Pate7STp8G8oApiZAu-koj4aeWQvM/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liberty of thought and expression &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/14ZZb2OLROlVcw6a-91BSRn57speIPU0XXb5EStqZ2Lg/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting self-determination &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/11NUHdUJe4QTtWpOfK4X1c64AvQr1K9bjX6Vt2m0wSBU/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Science and Technology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communication, technology, and extremism &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/14XEiC-S6xIkpkyWDJmOT7IXcxgZm1AONXFpuX0bx9xY/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equality of access to the digital world &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WLcDjgme4m2yDMn-edBqlwGZx8eFIshr86M2UAtRyNk/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The place of ethics in science &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FL1hp3NbP3HhqHZAKZSblsOJbrW1EzSsKN8c7KviW7A/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Click here to access the research report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Learn how to Debate]]></title><description><![CDATA[How to successfully prepare for ILYMUN To guarantee the excellence and the effective functioning of our ILYMUN debates, prior to the event…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/debate-help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/debate-help/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;How to successfully prepare for ILYMUN&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To guarantee the excellence and the effective functioning of our ILYMUN debates, prior to the event, we greatly encourage all students partaking in the conference to thoroughly prepare themselves. This will enable all to reap benefit from the experience!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To help our delegates in preparing for the conference, we have produced an effective five-step plan of action, to enable students to arrive at the conference in full confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Investigate your country’s background profile:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better start somewhere! Try looking into the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Political situation and active positioning; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Its interaction with neighbouring countries, the former’s influence, conflicts…; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Statistical facts and data: life expectancy, literacy rates, CO2 emissions, access to water…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; remember to follow current and ongoing actuality around your country, grasping current political tensions, newly introduced measures…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. UN Committee basics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to research your committee and its particular relevance with ILYMUN’s general theme, ‘Water: a thirst for change’. Look into:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  How does it differentiate itself from other UN committees? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  What are the committee’s current activities, actions and engagements? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  What is your country’s involvement and interactions with the UN committee?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. RRR: Read the Research Reports:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your committee’s research reports have for objective of supplying a general background and impression of your allocated UN committee’s topic, actuality and basic data. This step is crucial for understanding the topic at hand. Look out for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  The core issues of your topic; Key terms; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Data concerning other countries in the committee; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Future steps and issues to tackle; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Further reading linked in the research reports by your chairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Grapple your country’s positioning:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the debate, you’ll be representing your country and promoting its engagements. Look into:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Active engagements and policies; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Past issues revolving around the topic; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Identify allied countries and research accords; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  If there is lacking information for your country, research neighbouring countries’ situation(s).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These steps will enable you to begin thinking of potential resolutions to exhibit during the debates. Bear in mind, you should aim to produce action! How can this follow through in your resolutions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Familiarise yourself with the rules of procedure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a key component towards guaranteeing a delegate’s effective preparation towards the ILYMUN conference. Bearing in mind, the delegates are free to question their respective chairs before and during the conference for all their doubts and concerns. Chairs are here to help!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  Peer below to find an exhaustive explanation of procedures during an ILYMUN type-debate;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-  The following video equally provides a helpful visualisation of the main rules of procedure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RQIbx4s8YTw&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;720px&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;allowfullscreen&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/Rules-and-Procedures.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;../assets/ILYMUN-rules-and-procedure.pdf&quot;&gt;Click here to view the pdf version of the ILYMUN rules and procedures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Must know Concepts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Points &amp;#x26; Motions: What are they and how are they used?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a guide for first time delegates who aren’t completely familiar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;with all the different&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;or&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;motions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;at an MUN conference.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The difference between a motion and a point is who it concerns. A motion involves the entire committee, while a point only involves a chair or delegate. For this reason a motion requires a vote.  When a delegate proposes a motion, the chairs ask if there are any objections to the motion. If there are none, the motion is voted on. Neither points nor motions can interrupt speakers, unless it is a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;point of personal privilege&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to do with the audibility of the speaker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Motions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;When a delegate proposes a motion, another delegate must second it before the chairs will consider it and ask if there are any objections to the motion.  If there are objections, then the motion is dropped. If there aren’t any objections, there is a vote, without abstentions.  The motion passes if there are more votes in favour of the motion than against. All motions can be overruled by the chair.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to extend debate time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If passed this motion extends the amount of time allocated to the current clause or amendment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to table the amendment or clause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion is passed debate on the current clause or amendment is stopped without a vote or postponed until later.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to reconsider an amendment or clause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion is passed debate on an amendment or clause that failed or has been tabled is resumed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motion to move to previous question&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If this motion passes debate on the current amendment or clause is stopped, there is a  vote and the debate moves on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Points:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a question for the delegate who has the floor. The chair will ask the delegate if she is open to any points of information. If she is, she can state how many questions she’ll entertain or even say “any and all”. The chairs then ask if there are any points of information in the house.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of personal privilege.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This point is only used if a delegate is experiencing discomfort or cannot hear the delegate talking. This is the only point or motion that can interrupt the speaker, if it refers to the audibility of the speaker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of parliamentary inquiry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A point of parliamentary inquiry is a question about the rules and procedures of a debate, and can only be asked when there is nobody on the floor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point of order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A point of order refers to when a chair or a delegate makes a mistake. For a chair, this could be that he has made an error in the procedures, and for a delegate, it might be that he is doing something that his country would not do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;MUN Support:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, to ensure a high quality of debates, an External MUN Development team is dedicated to offering full assistance in building and/or developing MUN clubs for participating schools in need. If you are concerned, you may contact them through the ILYMUN support email address: support@ilymun.org&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dressing]]></title><description><![CDATA[During ILYMUN, delegates and members of the organising team are expected to have a professional attitude. This should reflect in their…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/dress/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/dress/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;During ILYMUN, delegates and members of the organising team are expected to have a professional attitude. This should reflect in their clothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attendees are requested to wear appropriate attire. Here is some inspiration on what to wear:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Clothes mean nothing until someone lives in them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ &lt;em&gt;Marc Jacobs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/ilymun-website/static/media/dresscode.ab5d389e.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gallery]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/gallery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/gallery/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/child1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:20%;width:20%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/flag1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:22.5%;width:22.5%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/flag2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:22.5%;width:22.5%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/flag3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:22.5%;width:22.5%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;padding-top:5px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/fun1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:22.5%;width:22.5%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/special-conf1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:22.5%;width:22.5%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/undp1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:20%;width:20%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/undp2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:20%;width:20%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;padding-top:5px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/ga1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:17%;width:17%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/who1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:25.5%;width:25.5%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/human1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:25.5%;width:25.5%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/isl1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:25.5%;width:25.5%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;padding-top:5px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/main1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:20%;width:20%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/main2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:26.7%;width:26.7%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/silent1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:13.4%;width:13.4%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://ilymun.org/images/gallery-img/silent2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture&quot; style=&quot;height:26.7%;width:26.7%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;padding-top:20px;&quot;&gt;If you want to see more pictures: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/internationallyonmun&quot;&gt;Click here for link to facebook.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;test&quot; style=&quot;visibility:hidden;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://google.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Help]]></title><description><![CDATA[2 place de Montréal, 69007, Lyon FRANCE]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/help/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Email&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ILYMUN Support email address: &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20181108191113/mailto:support@ilymun.org&quot;&gt;support@ilymun.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Mail&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cité Scolaire Internationale de Lyon,  International School of Lyon,
&lt;p&gt;2 place de Montréal,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;69007, Lyon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FRANCE   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Payment information&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Payment is to APESA (IBAN/RIB available &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20181108191113/http://ilymun.org/static/RIB-APESA.pdf&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[International Court of Justice]]></title><description><![CDATA[International Court of Justice WHAT IS THE ICJ ? The International Court of Justice is the principal judicial organ of the United Nations…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/international-court-of-justice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/international-court-of-justice/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Court of Justice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT IS THE ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The International Court of Justice&lt;/strong&gt; is the principal judicial organ of the United Nations. It pivots multinational disputes and safeguards nations’ sovereignty by settling legal altercations presented to it by the Member States. It does so by considering previous treaties, international conventions and international law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ICJ at ILYMUN will help you view conflicts from a new perspective and will offer insight on international law and the proceedings of judicial cases. The ICJ is perfect for those interested in international relations, law or simply for those who want to try something new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT IS THIS YEAR’S CASE ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year consists of two cases, each one with its own team:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Case 1:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Russian Federation versus The United States of America,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the conflict over the alleged Russian interference in the 2016 USA elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two teams of advocates will represent the following groups :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Applicant party: United States of America (USA)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Respondent party: Russian Federation (Russia)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Case 2:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Islamic Republic of Iran versus the United States of America,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the assassination of the Iranian General by US drone&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two teams of advocates will represent the following groups :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Applicant party: The Islamic Republic of Iran (Iran)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Respondent party: The United States of America (USA)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW DOES THE ICJ AT ILYMUN WORK ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The International Court of Justice is composed of:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;The Presidency:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year they are represented by Lisa Matimati, Belal Mohamed, Roman Harding and Vanessa Chioaru.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;The Advocacy:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An Applicant and a Respondent party, both represented by 2 advocates each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;The Jurisdiction:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A court of 15-20 independent judges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both advocate parties hold opening speeches, to present both factual and legal evidence to the judges. The judges are given time to question the advocates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, each advocate team presents two to four witnesses. (Witnesses are approved by the Presidents of the ICJ prior to the conference.) Advocates are given the opportunity to interview witnesses and then judges can also question the witnesses or pose questions to the advocates regarding witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then advocates present closing statements. After this, the judges deliberate upon the information presented to them and compose a verdict expressing their judgment in the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW DO ADVOCATES AND JUDGES PREPARE FOR THE ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advocates&lt;/strong&gt; need to research the case and create a report (called a memorandum). They also suggest a list of 3-4 supposed witnesses they would like to have at the trial. Finally, they create an evidence packet. The 2 parties collaborate together to create a stipulation. In sum, both teams prepare by:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Gathering evidence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Bringing in “witnesses”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Writing a stipulation, together&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Writing a memorandum&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Presidents of the ICJ will offer unbiased help and guidance to the&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;advocates. They will provide templates for the various documents and work in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;partnership with the advocates to create and polish these documents. The&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presidents will then share the documents with the opposing advocates and the&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;judges and/or post them on the ILYMUN website for all to access once the Trial is near..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Judges&lt;/strong&gt; should read the documents shared and posted by the Presidents of the ICJ to become familiar with the case, the witnesses and the evidence. It is expected that judges will act without bias, be reflective and innovative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presidents of the ICJ&lt;/strong&gt; will also guide the judges in their &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;deliberation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to help them evaluate legal documents and assure the quality of the final verdict.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOW DO I SIGN UP FOR THE ICJ ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delegates who want to apply to the ICJ should be confident in their level of English. Advocates in particular should be confident public speakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the challenging nature and limited places for this committee we ask delegates to apply for a role in the ICJ, by &lt;strong&gt;submitting a letter of motivation&lt;/strong&gt; which explains:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Their previous MUN experiences&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- What makes them interested and qualified for the role&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delegates should also state which role they prefer (&lt;em&gt;judge or advocate&lt;/em&gt;) and if they are open to taking the &lt;em&gt;alternative&lt;/em&gt; if they aren’t accepted for their first choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;any questions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; about the ICJ or &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;letters of application&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; before October 20 to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Belal.mohamed@csilyon.fr&quot;&gt;Belal.mohamed@csilyon.fr&lt;/a&gt; - General reference and Case 1 president&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Lisa.matimati@csilyon.fr&quot;&gt;Lisa.matimati@csilyon.fr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:romanh@islyon.org&quot;&gt;romanh@islyon.org&lt;/a&gt; - Case 2 presidents&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mini Ilymun The Conference]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/mini-ilymun-the-conference/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/mini-ilymun-the-conference/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More modest than ILYMUN, Mini-ILYMUN as a conference aims to recreate the spirit of ILYMUN on a smaller scale, bringing together around 60 delegates. The conference will be happening on the 5th of June, just before the school year ends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Born out of the desire to offer delegates something to look forward to despite current sanitary restrictions and the cancelling of ILYMUN 2021, Mini-ILYMUN strives to be both intellectually stimulating but also a friendly and communal space where students can interact and exchange. We hope for Mini ILYMUN to become an annual event; giving delegates a taste of what the real ILYMUN to come will be like, as it is placed at the mid-way point between ILYMUN conferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mini ILYMUN will take place from 9am to 4pm (9h-16h). The Cité Scolaire Internationale de Gerland and the International School of Lyon have invited the Nazarbayev Intellectual School from Kazakhstan to participate as well as our usual ILYMUN school partners, to ensure diversity among the delegates and their point of views. Students from grade 9 to grade 12 (3ème to Terminale) are welcome to participate. This conference will be the occasion for our delegates to debate as well as get to know each other, meet inspiring guest speakers, and, through an interactive time, discuss the resolutions that have emerged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Others MUNs]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/others-muns/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/others-muns/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Over the years, our students have gone to several MUN conferences, all around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;BERMUN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Berlin MUN conference is organised by the Friedrich-Ebert-Stiftung andthe John F. Kennedy School in Berlin, Germany&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://bermun.de&quot;&gt;Click here for link to the website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;INOMUM&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The International Nord MUN is organised by the International British Sections of the Lycée International Montebello and the Lycée Wallon in Lille, France&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.inomun.com/&quot;&gt;Click here for link to the website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;HMUN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Haarlem MUN conference is organised by the Stedelijk Gymnasium Haarlem, the Netherlands&lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hmun.nl/&quot;&gt;Click here for link to the website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;THIMUN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hague International MUN conference runs in Singapore, The Hague and Qatar &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://foundation.thimun.org/&quot;&gt;Click here for link to the website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;TIMUN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turkish International MUN conference is organised by the Uskudar American Academy, in Istanbul, Turkey &lt;br /&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.timun.gen.tr/&quot;&gt;Click here for link to the website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;MUNNISA&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The MUN conference is organised by the Nazarbayev Intellectual school in Aktau, Kazakhstan&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://munnisa.kz/&quot;&gt;Click here for link to the website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;LYMUN&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Lyons Township MUN conference is organised by the Lyons Township High School in Chicago&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lths.net/Page/11021&quot;&gt;Click here for link to the website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Poster Gallery]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/poster-gallery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/poster-gallery/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;div class=&quot;wrapper&quot; style=&quot;display:grid;grid-template-columns:repeat(3,1fr);grid-gap:10px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;../../../static/images/poster2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img href=&quot;/uploads/affiche-ilymun-2014.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The ILYMUN Team]]></title><description><![CDATA[Executive Team: Marine Balaÿ Sarah Cotte Raphaëlle Muller-Feuga Mathilde Le Luyer  Tomas Gouveia Emma Andreetta  Maja Muszyński  Heads of…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/team/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/team/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Executive Team:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marine Balaÿ &lt;br/&gt;Sarah Cotte &lt;br/&gt;Raphaëlle Muller-Feuga &lt;br/&gt;Mathilde Le Luyer &lt;br/&gt; Tomas Gouveia&lt;br/&gt; Emma Andreetta &lt;br/&gt; Maja Muszyński &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heads of Chairs:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sarah Matmati &lt;br/&gt; Claude Goni &lt;br/&gt; Tanya Kumble &lt;br/&gt; Chloe Marielle &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heads of Logistics:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mathilde Le Luyer &lt;br/&gt; Tristan Fournier&lt;br/&gt; Judy Sultan &lt;br/&gt; Lewis Cox &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Communications Team:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Giulia Olearo &lt;br/&gt; Eva Gromb &lt;br/&gt; Inès Fodor &lt;br/&gt; Clara Marsal &lt;br/&gt;  Titouan Rérolle &lt;br/&gt; Malak Malkawi &lt;br/&gt; Tahel Tobi &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heads of Youth Conference:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stéphane Vanoosthuyse &lt;br/&gt;
Patricio Andujar Salas &lt;br/&gt;
Kim Anna Giang &lt;br/&gt;
Carlota Ortega-Faurie &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Head of Press:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clara Larsen &lt;br/&gt; Caroline Tintinger &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heads of Audiovisual Press:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nathalia Kawarski &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heads of Written Press:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mae-Line Provoost &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heads of Admins:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorraine Brisset &lt;br/&gt; Violène Bertolino &lt;br/&gt; Daehun Kim &lt;br/&gt; Julien Chaussin &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heads of Action Assembly:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lila Schwab &lt;br/&gt;
Anna L’huillier &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heads of International Court of Justice:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa Matmati &lt;br/&gt; Bela Mohamed &lt;br/&gt; Roman Harding &lt;br/&gt; Vanessa Chioaru &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Graphic Designer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisa Nicol &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Committees and Issues]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/the-committees-and-issues/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/the-committees-and-issues/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conference will focus on three main issues: Refugees and the impact of COVID-19, Protecting the rights of refugee women and Empowering refugees through technology. For each issue, there will be a corresponding committee, which will lobby and debate on the topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These issues are strongly tied to our present times with the drastic consequences of the pandemic on those that were already struggling. Containing and preventing the spread of COVID-19 in packed refugee camps is a unique problem, which demands sufficient access to testing, areas for refugees to isolate themselves in, and vaccination. In a context in which access to healthcare for refugees is already heavily compromised, it is crucial to take note of the impact of the pandemic of Covid-19 on refugees - from the perspective of health, but also employment, border crossing, and social inclusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, as refugee conditions deteriorate, women are in greater danger than ever and face many obstacles on their journey. Refugee women are especially vulnerable, often being subject to sexual violence and sexism, both from their home country and their destination country. Generally fulfilling caretaking roles, protecting refugee women also means protecting refugee children, and the refugee community as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, as technology becomes a bigger part of our everyday lives, it is important to consider the impact, benefits and difference it could have on refugees. Access to an internet connection and mobile phones is crucial for refugees, notably to be able to use government services targeted to asylum seekers. Additionally, the Internet allows for refugees to study online for free, and research their rights in their destination country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All these themes are central questions that structure today’s debates and the world of tomorrow, hence the importance of discussing them among the youth, who will one day be policy-makers and community leaders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The UNHCR Challenge]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/the-unhcr-challenge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/the-unhcr-challenge/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;section&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mini ILYMUN is also an opportunity for us to participate in the UNHCR MUN Refugee Challenge. This challenge is hosted by the UNHCR and allows the resolutions that will emerge from the conference to be examined by a jury, composed of UNHCR members, young refugee leaders and independent experts. The best resolutions will then be shared with policy makers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a wonderful opportunity to move our delegates&apos; research, actions and debates into the increasingly important realm of international policy development. It is also a fantastic opportunity for our delegates to get closer to the real UN, bringing them a step forward towards concrete change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our participation in this challenge also allows us to increase our visibility as an MUN Conference, as in the past over 20 thousand students have participated in the event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, it is a fantastic avenue through which we can have a larger impact and share our voice and ideas with current world leaders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[about]]></title><description><![CDATA[“The cyber world is a sort of the Wild, Wild West, and to some degree, we’re asked to be the sheriff” - Barack Obama at Stanford University…]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/about/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The cyber world is a sort of the Wild, Wild West, and to some degree, we’re asked to be the sheriff” - Barack Obama at Stanford University, February 13th 2015&lt;/em&gt;.’&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 20th century technological revolution, and especially the invention of the internet, brought about a new wave of globalization and the creation of a new space called the “cyber world”. The Covid-19 pandemic has shown how much we rely on technology and to what extent we are all connected. As the cyber world affects so many aspects of our lives, it must be considered when working towards the United Nations’ goals. As Obama’s quote implies, the cyber world is a new frontier for which we need to develop institutions that are lawful, inclusive and fair. Therefore, our conference will focus on the United Nations’ Sustainable Goal 16, “Peace, Justice, and Strong Institutions” with debates focused on strengthening our cyber institutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will tackle some obvious global issues such as human and arms trafficking, extremism, the environment and the transparency of information, as well as philosophical and moral issues that explore the ethics of the cyber world and its consequences on individuals, societies and governments. All the issues stem from a greater question about the “Wild, Wild West” of the Cyber world: Are truth, justice, and peace in the balance? This year’s theme will foster intellectually stimulating debates as well as a creative space for personal development. We are ‘digital natives’, directly impacted and even formed by the internet and social media. Debating the cyber world in a formal setting should encourage us to take more responsibility in the use and development of these technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At ILYMUN, we believe that by involving youth in finding solutions and taking action, we can make a difference. Therefore, in addition to our core MUN committees, we will again host the Action Assembly, in which students represent themselves rather than countries in order to work towards real change in their local communities, the International Court of Justice and the Youth Conference for “collège” or middle school students from the Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes region.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Contact]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/contact/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/contact/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No title]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/countdown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/countdown/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Our Sponsors]]></title><description><![CDATA[image1: logo_apesa.png image2: logo_csi.png image3: logo_mdl.png image4: logo_riso.png]]></description><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/our-sponsors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/our-sponsors/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;image1: logo_apesa.png&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;image2: logo_csi.png&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;image3: logo_mdl.png&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;image4: logo_riso.png&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[By Students for Students]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/parallax/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/parallax/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Press]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/press/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/press/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Our Team]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/team/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/team/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why ILYMUN?]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/values/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/values/</guid><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mini Ilymun 2021]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/mini-ilymun-2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/mini-ilymun-2021/</guid><pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ILYMUN 2021]]></title><link>https://ilymun.org/home-page/hero/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ilymun.org/home-page/hero/</guid><pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>